Tannaz Shirzadi

Frontend Developer

Sht. Oguz Parpaloglu Cd, Pinartepe, Buyükcekmece, Istanbul, Turkey (+90) 536-582-2392

tia.shr97@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tannaz-shirzadi

SUMMARY

Meticulous and ambitious Front-end developer with about six years of experience in providing high-impact web solutions and mobile-first web applications for diverse industry organizations, facilitating projects from concept to launch, optimizing existing projects and proficient in modern libraries. Critical thinker with an instinct for design who plans to use these qualities in a Front-end developer role that allows me to further develop my skills.

EXPERIENCE

Windranger Labs, Remote - Front-End Developer (Contranct, Remote)

FEBRUARY 2023 - AUGUST 2023

- Used Nextjs 13 features and migrate pages into the App directory using app router to optimize previous code and create Server Components and Suspense.
- Worked heavily on Directus CMS development as super admin and developed custom modules.
- Developed various application functionalities such as search, server-side pagination and filtering using url params.
- Used existing components in MDX to blend markdown and JSX syntax.
- Used Server-side rendering to make the website SEO friendly.
- Implemented different reusable and responsive components for data visualization using Tailwind such as charts, carousels cards and more.
- Managed multilingual translation using i18nexus
- Used both Graphql and custom API endpoints to interact with data.

Informatics Services Corporation, Tehran - Front-End Developer (Full-Time, Remote)

JULY 2021 - December 2023

- Identified and implemented dynamic web solutions in accordance with company standards.
- Enhanced the React observables with Redux, React-router and Redux thunk.
- Implemented a new responsive website approach which increased mobile traffic by 30%.
- Involved Webpack as module bundler to preprocess and minify different files such as TypeScript and SASS files
- Built two reusable design libraries, using Storybook.
- Created new features, and functionality using React, Typescript, Redux, Router, and styled components.
- Created a custom client dashboard that reduced support tickets by about 25%
- Used JavaScript library Jest for the unit testing

Stage Try, Toronto - Front-End Developer (Full-Time, Remote)

MARCH 2021 - JUNE 2021

- Introduced Kanban board style ticketing system to increase efficiency.
- Boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 60% with improved code and design.
- Acquired experience with Next.js, Typescript, Storybook, Jira and Tailwind.
- Created user-friendly forms using React-Hook-Form, Yup and Antd.
- Developed state management workflows and implemented them over the React Js.
- involved in daily SCRUM meetings to keep track of the ongoing project status and issues.

SRICO (Soroosh Rayaneh Iranian), Tehran - Front-End Developer (Full-Time)

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2021

- Utilized HTML, CSS, SASS and javascript to create responsive landing pages.
- Used understanding of React fundamentals to promote better component lifecycle practices.
- Migrated a multi-page user experience into a single page app which improved customer engagement by 14% using React.
- Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 30%.
- Implemented mobile applications using React Native from concept through deployment.
- Acquired experience with redux and middlewares such as Saga and Thunk.

Rayan Gostar Novin Pardazan Bakhtar, Kermanshah - Front-End Developer (Full-Time)

SEPTEMBER 2015 - DECEMBER 2019

- worked closely with business leaders.
- Monitored website performance and rectifying front-end issues.
- Turned design pages and specific components into HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Experienced installing and using SASS.

SKILLS

React Js, React Native, Next.js, Typescript, Javascript, Redux, Thunk, Saga, Webpack, Graphql Storybook, Styled Components, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Antd, Agile, Scrum, HTML, CSS, SASS

EDUCATION

Kermanshah University of Technology (KUT), Kermanshah- Bachelor's Degree (Computer

Engineering - Information Technology)

SEPTEMBER 2015 - FEBRUARY 2019

Relevant Coursework: Fundamentals of Computer and Programming, Advanced Programming,

Data Structures, Algorithms Design, Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems, Database,

Computer Systems Security, Operating Systems, Computer Networks

Languages

English: Fluent **Persian:** Native